The wound who use it
who's who's. Who's
who's who and who's who's.
At who's
what
who's who's. Who
who's. Who who's
losing. It who's
to. Know where. This
is where I live I'm
a housewife My name is Alan Jones That's
Tuesday and July I started out just like
any other day the past few months there
was no warning it was to be the most
terrifying day of my life I remember
thinking how tired I felt even the housework
seemed drudgery so meaningless with George
confined to his bed no one to see her
care even and then I got scared because I
knew I was beginning to feel sorry for
myself George was the one who was ill
and he needed all of my thoughts and
attention and above all my cheerfulness
I tried not to think about George how
he'd change I told myself it was just my
imagination that things would be different
when he was well and strong again
then I thought I heard him call
you or did you call
George are you alright.
Yes hello. You want anything now I've just
begun work on assurance report for the
office well call my
dear if you need me OK.
When I have to you it was something
about George's voice. I found myself
thinking about the first.
One. I remember I was
sitting in Dr Graham Bell we were talking
I played one game of checkers and took
aim to from me and I've written letters to
Lady wife the mother of this week and I
this is what happened to homesick young
ensign from Texas. Now what else could I do
to help boost the morale around here. We
get about halfway through this if you get
a call from the hospital. I guess my
courting will have to wait till after the
house to. The compound fracture down the
hall is waiting to see me but I'll be tied
up for a while to tell me feeling blue
you see his wife expecting a baby in
a minute and I think you just joining us.
Oh I'm sorry they tell me I can find Dr
Gray but you ought to be along any minute
want to come on I'm sure thank you for
your patient yes or. They will hospital.
I'm just a friend of the
doctor so when last night was
a Saturday coming up. Wrong With Me was
a double barrel. Too That's right I will
be detained so I'm taking you for being
maybe he doesn't want to go front
of him he doesn't not like
a woman likes better than shoving
a man around. Hello
. To you and I'm.
Such
a tool as much to play sorry to tell my
parents about it but they're still back in
Kansas City now looking to do.
Because I get a lot of things
a little. Shall we begin with a
game of cat. Like I could read
a newspaper to you I could write
a letter for you I know I know I'm right
here you can tell me all about that
wonderful baby you expect. The baby
you think does Ripley know about this
I think if I. Skip this. Which is your
bad leg Well neither one of them
is working very well today.
Is your head bothering you terribly both
of them. Would you like me to read that
story you can think of
anything nice and. How relaxed
approach right now just
think of something.
Pretty soon you're going around your
way that the one. Think which is
a. Pretty sure. Lovely beautiful blue I'm
sure no. Soft brown hair. Lovely blue.
Well there's nothing wrong with your morale
young man I recommend of the doctor to
be sent home to your wife
immediately. So you wait
a minute you're all naturally drawn out
right but I forget what you're doing here
enjoying myself and that's
really just like isn't
a broken you know no way Doc what kind of
nurses do you have around it anyway it
was on your own but when I came out here
he was lying there all covered up and let
me make an absolute idiot of myself rubbing
his head both of them the best cure in
the world for I go but I'm not George Jones
at all an untrustworthy friend of mine
I remember I saw him first you know it's
just the names of two presently completely
understand wished I
wouldn't say that I. Am
a wind up wearing it but. So I go.
To ask you. Pretty surprising
having a medical student for
a roommate he was always suspecting something
pulling me I don't know what's going
on inside of expect understand
after. My service for want of
a hospital there's an emergency all right
I'm sorry Oh my well back to the top mind
you folks later oh I can help but. I intend
to give you that myself for the rest of
the afternoon and for the next two weeks.
And I'll only prospect of strikes gold he
doesn't feel for his friends expects
acclaimed so much yes I love it I don't like
to make love on an empty stomach when I
do I specially to say I think strange my
hell and whatever did you get the idea that
I was blessed and so you would you like
to switch boxes like we did when we were
kids that you know. Remember some of the
meadows cookies. A ration of canned
ham foundered milk chewing gum and
four cigarettes and coffee. Honestly is
that the best you can do the best I could
do with no rush and now if we were to
combine forces pull out of those. I
think we might do very well together.
There are good luck my
friend. Right after.
Taking. Me Back coming
remember that I'll be back.
Never let you go.
To guy. I'm going to
marry him when you marry him
just because. I figured as much.
For you here is right for you. I don't
know. Something you think about is just
something you you know. You
can't do anything about.
I don't want to make. A guy was playing it
out it all over us fellows I walk around
down here.
I'm coming up now here you want
me to bring you anything so.
What it was a man going
to duck. Down on I get
a doctor another doctor not going to have
to deal here George I don't argue with me
don't call Graham get another doctor.
Holy Thanks. For the good.
QUESTION But I think.
Sounds pretty good.
Better than at one. Time.
It took
a long time to get it running seems like
it but it seems as soon as I can. How long
did it take. Fortunately I was
living on another call. On
a bus. Today no forty five minutes
ago but it's still
a thing I. Always
know best out. I just know that he comes.
Running the talk to each other we both
know my own insurance company wouldn't put
me out of all of us in the
same boat. And I'm expecting.
A condition like yours. That
doesn't necessarily mean
a member. Think of all the chatter you
took during the war you didn't worry about
them came out feeling better when you went
to. The only thing you have to do is lie
here in bed and I hope you get well it's
not right and yes I can tell you you're
lucky in many ways to. That wonderful
wife she developed into fine art I don't
think I'll be tying up our exclusive
services much longer. You've got to cut out
this way of thinking. That you
might like to talk to George and.
Those were pretty morbid things you were
saying in front of Ellen she complained
certainly but you got to think
of her too she's looking
a little worn when you get
these ideas try using
a little mental therapy Next you'll
be telling me I ought to see
a psychiatrist I'd be
a very good idea doctors are all alike you
can't cure the patient you're telling us
all of this mind I'm trying to
help you Joyce you know that. I'll
drop in again this afternoon that we
can talk this thing out maybe we can.
I'm going to do anything particular
happen to upset charges for. No matter.
What you think you were.
I don't like is not.
Mean it's just. Very active in my
head it's natural for me to grasp.
What Amanda
a lot of mentally and physically prone
to all sorts of imaginary fears. I
feel better if you were in the hospital
for one. No I don't think so or you want
what's best for George talks report of
course that's just it. I think what upset
him you see he doesn't seem to want
anyone else around him except me. With
a smile he didn't even want me to call
you. Always the soil around at last count.
Likely to take
a dislike to if you. Look up to
enjoy Chargers patients your
friend George is up there promoting. The
developments which. You will send him to
the hospital I want you to have one your
company. I'm sure you know what's best for
him but honestly I don't know how George
will tell you but he doesn't even seem to
want to add around and I don't think it's
wise for you to try to how this will only
go after you're stressed to the breaking
point all right I'll take it up with
George have to know. I gotta get
back upstairs no remarks for.
The medicine chest. I
want you to relax to.
Remember now you're a calm in
a time you need even if you just thank
you thank you I don't know what I do
sometimes and I didn't
remember that. Going on.
As we was so. Frightened. Yeah.
What are you all dressed up for and where
did you get that beautiful new Try thing
called the price of well below zero
how men are like that funny oh you
did what
a beautiful filly I'm feeling
I'm happy now who's happy
don't you know who coffee No I'm
pretty I don't. Wanna go to my home no
one feed my you're. Looking
well when you look at that
a coffee fair to get
a wife in the Whale Shark Tank course I
know him that's not for long Cassidy. Well
they had many people today happy oh thank
you I did go try to take down Oh I
wouldn't think of it you have
a cookie No I haven't to go Sherman hasn't
come yet but I will have later. You know
there's a beverage you
know what do you do I buy
a little piece of china I'm in jail oh I
don't think the real happy treat even bad
men. Who were weary what I
did was my fill time up
the moment yeah that sounds like
a lot more work and more dangerous to. Take
care of everybody yeah you sure did you
know. Well honey I'm sorry I'm afraid that
my husband isn't feeling very well today
I won't make any noise if I would be killed
he begged to be because no you could
but I'll tell you what to do after the
grocery man comes out to be around twelve
o'clock see you come back to
a very quietly and I have some cookies for
you OK OK I met her now to see that no
bad people making me know that you're fat
I'm sorry but try to have that you're my
friend. And then I did
and then having done.
Let you know who you want to
have been just not right. Oh
it must be the heat I coulda sworn I saw
somebody right all I think took you so
long. I was talking to Billy I
should say how to change or come
here he good little boy I told you about
who just moved into the neighborhood the
woman the black ice and off with that OK
But we're talking to Remy Graham about
that's what I'm interested in we were talking
about you do you. Think you were too
much for. I didn't I don't know who would.
Joy ever since you got out of bed yesterday
if you could walk ahead on the line I
want you to promise me not to get out of
bed again when I'm out of the room All
right Eleanor. Did you call the druggist
about getting the prescription filled
yesterday for the sender that later in the
day but there's nothing else we needed
before to tell him I spilled it no I
didn't feel well enough for the paper.
Yeah. I did try OK your front
page is all right thank you.
You look tired Allen.
Coming out of the South.
What are you thinking about it like
well you know I was just think you had
everything and I was every breath every
thought has been precious so I don't think
people can do that and be
happy that you are getting
a little confused doubting
it was me that ran
a great I'm told to change my way of thinking
Oh no no I mean it was my fault too.
I just wasn't strong enough to have that
we could change overnight. But make
all the difference in the world your arch
coming yes. What's the first thing you do
. But I'm out of this bed
again way from my house.
To be so grateful that you. I think
I try to do something to some
I mean you are your own
so. I'd like children.
And I'd like a garden
a real garden like the woman next door. I
find out about flowers and things and I
compare notes with every other
woman on the block so you have
a garden and children with me
could I have. Kind of gives you
something to hold on to that. Takes
a long time for things to sink in. But
you always said that you always make
a plan for everything and stick to
it. All right I have ten years to
get well. And then after much
think I'm very stupid. To think
I know you're in love with I'm never.
At the silliest I have ever
heard of you you're not
a socialist you think you are no
it's quite obvious. It's just
a choice but I realize it's more to do so
the point of my life is one day just mine
charge what are you talking about I almost
feel sorry for you well you are right
that you intend to see under-rated me you
haven't cut it for the intelligence you
think you have don't talk much do you suppose
I don't know he told you to rake over
these old coals this morning no dear he did
not answer me I was offended by making
me impossible promises I know something
about my own sickness. I know what happened
alright man when you take
a wife out for her I know what happens when
you constantly judge is this why don't
you think I have talked about. That's
what he told you to do if you know I also
tell you to delay getting help to me like
you did this morning how could you do
that Helen how could you take on that second
right you know if you will do anything
you say are going to go on for letting
yourself it's what your. Friends don't talk
too much.
You know and you just couldn't believe the
things you've said about Dr Drew I don't
even want to.
Leave it halfway up that line.
I was so hurt I could hardly keep from
crying. But again I reminded myself that
George was terribly ill
and he didn't mean it.
You. Know who's.
Who's who's. Up
for it
for.
Our way.
I knew I had to keep doing something
anything anything to keep me from hearing
George's words. He didn't mean he
couldn't be. It was just the he.
When I took his lunch after i'd be
pleasant and cheerful this is nothing it
happened. Thank you
for helping. Oh you don't
have to whisper now. I was
just thinking it's not. Going to your cooking
but this is a story that already had
a lot going on but you know I
want to give you. A catching
a cold and that's what. You saw just why
why God so I thought oh I did use that
to prevent somebody. Talking
how much I. Wonder what Thank
you for. That's very nice I'm
sure you don't want to keep
it yourself when you've got
a big bowl of this in there called already
a one this is just what I know it is but
it's very nice and I want to thank you
very much for giving it. And I'm just
always in school for when you say.
Bad hit like say I'm sick of my life we
look at the television so I stay in bed I
think I was
a very good idea I have to tell my husband
about it and I think I'm glad with it as
you can't go outside Well that's very
nice of you but I don't think he's well
enough people there I won't make it you
know I guess I'll just be like OK who looks
. Well let's you know we can do what he's
feeling better OK that was it I got to
say my whole life OK.
For. Him I think whom I was
oh by all means take advantage of by
other people all right. But how many
are you sure you want to make
a television set with these amazing music
but I'm not the break guy that he's like
well all right I'll tell you and
thank you again OK bye bye.
I always felt better if you talk to his
heart I wondered how he'd look without his
glasses. Tonight you think
you. Don't break it
I had to use it again. George Washington
lunch that was
a good sign. Really
much better. Copy center Press Television.
And he says not to break yet this year
that led to it going to be great but.
Darling this is so eager to please. All
right and this you're going to have to
be handsome face before
you. Postman coming
up. Postman as they come in.
Is
a must see to his. Image but I want
to go with. The question or risk.
Arrest. Relief to get the. New insurance
law fix the Amazon state I've got
a chuckle all right here.
I mean even the case.
If you think back to that train of thought
you know what happened the last time.
You really wrote
a letter to. You
know what.
I wanted to stop
a minute and Chuckles Maybe. But
I knew George wouldn't like. He
didn't believe in maybe.
And then I saw the post.
Where do you think this
is going to break. John
thank God sure. Actually with
a smile that like heavy are I hope I'm
all in Maulana what I'm going to be like
this afternoon I guess I'll live everything
so I've got to keep my nose to the
grindstone got a pension plan that I can
have yes you did well you gotta follow to
a T have responded come you know my wife
doesn't understand that she says I'm an
old penny pincher now
but I told her that's
a caution would you take that letter from
a place. Else where I bring in more mail
and I take oh I'm sorry I'd run up to the
mailbox with it myself but I don't like
to leave the house on my husband then you
know and I know never figures out slows me
up like you never got his will run this
off or he might see the problem your feet
ever go yeah I know just what you mean
you know I want to be
a pineapple numerics great the new when
I'm gone I won't be all that I want to
clock but what everybody giving me mail to
take back is that Matheny for me is that
my. That's not a retirement plan
a case may go on yeah I bet it is well
thanks again this again you're welcome. Glad
to see your husband's well enough to be out
Mrs Jones. I. Wish I could lie down for
a while. In the Lol where.
Joe if you were out there had promised you
know what you are going to bed Mike and
. Do you suppose until he saw you
at the window. Well he didn't
actually say you saw you post when you got
a touch or so struck. Me too I guess.
It does help to think. Thank
you. When you got that letter.
Come on to your island.
But you're like
a visitor who has it's pretty hard for
the love it is yes. The Afenifere I
you know I always was. And.
When I was crazy about my mother Stella
six gave me too much but I can still
remember that too in. The small absolutely
perfect sailing ship building side of it
. You know I was I was so crazy about
that one let anybody touch it not even
my mother. One day I
was making God. Making
a God and in the back it
a boy came running out of my house with
my ship and. Somehow I got away from him
and I like him. I don't know
what I said to him but.
Suddenly I was right into thinking he might
have broken the ship I mean. I picked
up the little rake I'd been playing with
and began hitting him with his face and
been so why did was so blind. And I
killed him. She took him into the
house into the bathroom life
to face the. Ship again.
The neighbor boy stopped crying mother
turned to me and she said give it to. To
kind of strange and quiet I knew I had
to. Say And I guess he hadn't learned
anything so I. And on the ship but just as
he was about to take it I let it drop on
the tile floor and I stepped on it. You
never know what it was but somehow or other
it's mine. Mine wasn't it ever been before
I remembered every little thing about it
. But then it was just
a mess of broken glass and matchsticks
on the floor. Telling me.
That. Very much in
a good. Dr Gray was going to find
himself in exactly the same point.
We're not going to have him. But that
doesn't change the fact that you're wrong
about him he's been wonderful to parts
of you so much time maybe that's because
he's a bachelor no home life he's been
a good friend to me. So you must
listen carefully any Graham
I have you are right. He'll
be disappointed when I get.
I can't talk this way more. I also have.
A better way to learn written that
district attorney ask him to make
a complete investigation if anything happens
to me today before he helped me why do
you talk to yourself like this why do you
imagine things that don't exist whether
exist it proves you're trying to kill me.
If I can help it I'm going to get someone
else in here because I made it made and
you gave that letter to the postman yourself
just when I go yes yes I gave him the
letter the one that you wrote about insurance
policy. I know you wouldn't recognize
a district attorney and nobody ever does
and that's right everybody knows there's
a district attorney but nobody ever knows
his name we are going to get another
doctor because this is all in your mind.
Just to reassure you want to point to
tell you that's what it was about shouldn't
I tell the district attorney how much
insurance we had only tell us lives of the
one of the other would do very nicely
for the rest of his life live very comfortably
Oh I also told him how you and Dr
Graham how you were. Working together that
aggravate my condition so it would look
like. I also told him how you
would. Gradually giving me
overdose and. That isn't true. Anyone
would know that isn't true with the.
Bottle most of. The day when.
You've got to just tell them to try
to tell the guy just not just until the
drugs that. The Phillips will like and I
witness against you well you'll be the
first if anything happens to me and let me
tell you they'll be other let it takes
care of everything that druggist the
medicine the doctor he's in the well you've
implicated your old friend Graham you
know nothing's going to happen to you
I don't know what you're doing it's
a bad you know but I'm going down doesn't
get that letter back in that post you're
not going anyplace anymore.
I'm going to kill you.
Definitely want to.
You mean this Georgia.
I wouldn't. Say much.
But you did. And that's why your.
Letter will take Graham I'll
take it if you might. Make it look like.
There are just too many things against.
What happened.
It was one of those. Kind I used to.
Joke.
When is it that you want.
To go. That is until I talk with.
My husband try to. But
that's what I have and I
probably should that's
what happens. How did I do
before because I didn't think
it was necessary. To be
a witness against. What.
I. Actually did to get
another perspective.
I didn't tell him that.
I had to. I couldn't tell anyone
about George is like that's not
a back the second deal the woman
next door walked. Maybe she'd be
a witness against me to the poor she could
tell him how I ran out of the house and
then back in again. A strange
way. It wouldn't matter much
if I could only. Try to
see which way to go.
The you're
one of our
role has
a whole. Back for. A
page everything went but I. Know.
That for me to continue coming to the
person with a pulse but yeah
yeah. That was wait to hear
a little while ago which way to go. That
away oh yeah that way towards America
street you know yeah I know.
I.
Was right you know every time I go home at
night I always tell my wife Laura if it
wasn't for that pension plan and I just
never good enough I just got my project one
of these days I'm not upset
a little I just never got up anymore and
that's all you know how I got in your
heart to feel like that you feel it was
off. During what are you doing now says was
. How visiting a friend that
night I wish I had more time for
a visit but by the time I got home with
my daughter yes hardly make it up the
stairs I tell my guy that me and that
letter I gave you this morning oh so I pick
up on the letters what I want above well
I have now it seems silly but I I made
a by mistake it was unfinished Yeah now
what did you do that for what I don't know
I guess why would you I already showed up
Mailer us to the Tomorrow they were given
the how you wouldn't want me to do that may
I have said that it's his. First I pick
him up you carry room for miles and then
I'm back again Paul I'm sorry but you can
understand why I would want to go out and
finish so that all these delays come you
know most people on the net of
a lot of probably much trouble one of the.
Banks Hello you shouldn't be giving me
this letter in the first place. Giving
me this letter just like putting it with
mailbox my you wouldn't
expect to get respect from
a mailbox would you know but you can
MAKE THIS IS SUCH AN after all.
Isn't this this fun of the district
attorney. Yes. Yes my head my husband read
about some graph in the newspaper and he
wrote to the district attorney about it oh
your husband wrote the letter but just
said you're older. Didn't think my husband
know it makes all the difference in the
world Mrs Jones was just one of our
strictest rules we can't return
a letter to anyone except the person who
wrote it. Took us to my husband you know
how did you get me to get the sign where
we go abstinence you know it's all right
he said at
a time have no idea like that after standing
here patiently and all is he trying to
reason with you you're the one is being
obstinate you don't seem to realize is
against the rules so how do you care for
this I guess rules I have to care but you
don't you're not the one
who gets prior. I'm sorry.
I forgot what it means to you your
responsibility is. To be this terrible he agrees
you know I just my husband has to get that
letter back it was my fault you see I'm
in the by mistake he's awfully upset with
me that angry with in the car going to
please help me. Please
have the letter pack well
a little bit yes well turn around told
Fafner delivery and since it's so important
like you say oh it is well if you give me
a lift back to town in your car sales I
won't lose any more time I will I'll go
over to your house with you right now and
give the letter to Mr Jones personally.
No no you can't put Mrs Jones this way
I'll be sticking to the rules of your
hospital get
a letter back but I haven't been asleep
last night and he told me just before I
left that I would want to wake you trying
to do the right thing by everybody
concerned for the Seems to me you don't
want to cooperate and I'm not going to risk
losing my job for anyone trying to understand
I can't talk about any longer than
waste any more time you want to take the
letter he doesn't personally or don't you
. I said I'll take the post office like
I'm supposed to you can go down there and
got it from the superintendent superintendent
Yes he's got more authority and I
have maybe he'll give it to you I think
it's better not waste any more time once I
bring the mail and I send it out right
quick once it leaves the post office the
delivery nobody can stop at the post office
downtown yeah. I want to go back to how
do I get there the shortest way I know right
on down the boulevard shortest gap Mr
Hanks how much time do I have
to haul Bob to thirty maybe
a little before. The
the.
Yellow. And.
The. Well worn.
Old.
PARTY Yes Have you seen Mrs so this morning
yes right out about half an hour ago
where all yes George Sr Joe Jackson gone
off left him alone as you well covered
securely so I've heard. I
never really met. A match
like that. With the Joneses
that I made in. Fact.
I would. I could tell you where
the key is. Think it's nosy but
I happened to see her
when she locked the door.
The door.
The top of the green shutters the far
side of the door. The good thing I can do
for you.
I mean all the speeches.
I'm going to go.
Whatever happened to them anyway I gave
you very little medicine all that tasted
good even the panic and no promises. And
I never sing in Exeter I am worn out on
just that doctor to give you something
cried All right that's allowed me to be
a good doctor and after all if you enjoy
it like I'm so much confidence that's half
the battle and you look up to see if you.
And letting yourself go like you do you
know I know I had terrible. When Job
the sleep why I had to marry and to do
I got to stop. I just thought I'd
go and take care of them without
bothering to change you know how to make
sure you're all right can I love to have
my gown for fifty I think it puts news
will do you good I'm not tired really am
well after all Claire I have so much
to do today the only other thing that
prevents you will be on your back before
you know if you don't watch out after all
I'm going to do is to help from now on I'm
going to have more time to tell and I
forgot to tell you I resigned resigned from
the help and you have to fifteen years
I'm not helping any more. I'll have
a kitchen door open and then we can
talk what I'm dreaming about there are
a lot of words yourself exactly zero zero
zero zero zero one zero you're free to
bring me
a god brought up the thing yet if I was in
that video and photographs I was Treasurer
and the last three days I will promise to
use the presidency so what happens if you
were sitting in that courthouse documents
that we've got his wife Well I feel
exactly what I was hasty to
fifteen years you know I'm
a little small woman yet I
was always boasting about
a little handsome tiny feet and trying to
run everything best I can I do think I
was brought. You know after all
that he says not ease up on
a flight activity not. He didn't stop I
just. Thought. I'd always
have you fly so much of his
day but that's just one of the what is the
thing that's an old American all out why
don't you have some of that the other
consummate Lisa was jealous when I left all
the private spaces and it's full of vitamin
I'd like something to enjoy after all
it's all in my face hope I think I'll
run out of coffee and on George if he's
asleep you can tell him later
that I think. It's bad
for him because there's something
I'm spending what is he what.
Are you having trouble. I didn't want to
tell you but now I think I must still
take my advice and don't believe the
following This is what you did I thought it
was funny your being out like that I'm not
going up to see George when you came in
but you don't understand why I don't just
say I'll just say goodbye now please
don't I did I didn't want to tell
you this but George said that that
when i was time you came to see him you
upset him terribly and he said to tell you
that if you came again to day to day and
he just couldn't say you upset him you
must remember he's
a coffee and I was glad to tell him so now
do you. Think you can hear the motor so
he knew I was here all the time but I don't
use Romanian So this was part of the
sixties role even suffered since he had
been sick I'm sorry I had to tell you this
but I thought when I first
met you to do something for
a change and saw how I was said You haven't
changed at all these was the thing I
doubt you can tell George Clooney but
a bad rep who felt like subset of
a small package. And
wondered how much time I
she was right I must with all I had to fix
myself up before I could go to the post
office I had to go and. I was
terrified but I knew I had to.
Charge. Because. I mustn't think about
anything anything until I get that
letter. Better that I killed.
They viewed.
A. Preventive. I get the other house
right making a simple request for
a letter
a letter that was mailed by mistake. In
Georgia. Somehow I know
I shouldn't leave it.
Sam yet he told me off the radio I
just turned it off you know I mean
no no no no I think they're all right I.
Prayed that no one else
had heard that shot.
I thought perhaps if I didn't enter he'd
think no one was home and he'd go. He
didn't he just rang the
bell again and then stood.
And I knew I had to get rid of him.
Good afternoon Mr Russell I'd like to
see Mr Jones is expecting me I think
yes he telephoned me the other day
well they must become mistake.
He was unable to leave his bed he
told me he was out but he didn't have
a phone to be here this
afternoon. Anyway it's
a business matter Mrs Jones I'm sorry but
the doctors had been to see you warning
that I get some resistance from you didn't
explain that you were over solicitous
about his health but that I wouldn't take
you seriously your husband only wants me
to authenticate the legal
papers I'm a notary one take
a few minutes I'm sorry I've already told
you I haven't got enough he said to read
that the doctor just after
a few minutes ago and he said he was not
going to see anyone today not anyone I'm
sorry to bother to Miss Jones That's all
right. Leave my card have to call me yes
yes I'll call you good afternoon.
He'd be another when. He cried I.
Have to be more careful.
A little fool of me are remembering what
happened last time I had to be sure no one
could get into the heart.
Of who is zero zero zero zero.
Zero Billy. Are you all
right. So I don't know you OK
I'm sorry I'm like I have a take be
more careful when it doesn't ever do
a thing like that again
you hear me OK that was
a problem coping well I'll give you some
more later on. Yes after that you say
reckon that's right way
to like about that OK.
All I remember about the Dr down time
was. I could take. This time I must.
I must keep calm.
We caught him plenty of time
Mr Jones has brought us
a little while ago wasn't even processed
and I can have it now of course.
I'm glad we caught him time for you my
husband will be so pleased to have that I'll
give you one of our regular four
mysterious four yes one of these oh.
You mean I can take the letter with my now
just take the form home to Mr Jones have
him for the thousand when you bring it
back I'll have it right here and I'll give
it to. But why is that just
regulations among other
things it will give me
a chance to compare Mr Jones's handwriting
with the writing on the envelope I can
hear us my husband handwriting sure yes
but I must have one of those forms for my
records Oh but. I haven't been very ill
and everything bothers him so and if I don't
have this metaphor and when I got home
he would be awfully upset why he
should well you see I'm afraid he said
a lot of very strong things and he regrets
the now you can explain to him that it
won't be delivered it'll be all right here
to live on comes back you know but it's
so hard to reason with
a person who's ill when you have already
had the. Exaggerate the importance of
everything what was his heart
condition I wouldn't take
a chance really I must have
a letter for him when I go home now I'm not
Mrs Jones I think I can take it should
I let you fill out the form for your husband
on one condition of course make sure
that the contents of the letter to me will
be strictly confidential but of course
the letter must be opened and read up and
then I said yes to make sure that there's
a letter to the district attorney you say
no no you're OK I think you're right I
don't try going to my house for the mail
you know I want to go back you want to
stone I don't think Mrs Jones I was about
to tell you if you'd let me finish that I
would call your husband for you explain
the situation reasonably and ask his
permission for you would
have over the letter not me.
I didn't say that. But you don't seem
to understand No I don't understand
Mr Jones. And I have no
alternative but to send
a letter on through the distributing the.
Old old old
old.
You know. If you don't. I don't want to
intrude I couldn't help noticing you all
day long I've had the feeling that you.
Something was wrong and I still like to be
able to help you. I know we haven't been
too neighborly
a couple something else again can I help
you. Is there something I can do for you.
I know you are anxious to get up to your
husband so you run after he's comfortable
and settled then you come over
our call I'll be waiting for.
She was kind. She might have been
my friend. She might have helped.
Mina remember Greg. He said he was going
to stop it against the George I couldn't
let him do that. You
mustn't come here. Ever.
Dr Graham's office. Oh you can hear
Mrs Jones can you locate him place
a surgeon. Please do
very important Dr Graham
doesn't come here today.
And I hope you understand. By.
That I don't call to all my just for those
words but well George felt he wanted to
consult another doctor and I did too and
he just left and and I think really think
that if you didn't see him again
today oh. But the doctor did you go
oh oh. I. Forgot his name I called him
a dentist or her doctor and she gave me
a telephone number and. George
liked him very much. Yes.
Oh yes yes that is I think so. What
was his diagnosis I don't know I've
already talked to feeling much better I'm
going to more about what I want
to happen. When you see after.
No no please don't. Read about
everybody just don't go out there.
He had to go and he tried
to kill me but this was
a good to each week. And
so I took the God's hand and I hid I had
to and this is how he died protecting
himself from me write him but why
did you want me. To tell you.
That letter said that we planned this
death to gether did you tell me that they
just condition you give him over doses of
the talk medicine and if they come here
and find tell you it doesn't disturb just
I just said come on his mind was gone I
tried to tell you this morning it wasn't
responsible and don't believe me How could
this I did everything wrong everything
just like you said I was the druggist man
the postman and then the superintendent
I've been lied to was I don't think I was
guilty although you're not guilty remember
that when I know the police will be here
any minute now you gotta go you
gotta go right. I'm going to go.
I don't know there's no sense
in running away now with
a job. I don't.
Well Mrs Jones I got
a letter for the SAS No I didn't put it in
the slot because when I I guess I should
feel kind of funny coming here like this
after what happened between you and me
just know that it's all right
I am still alive. There's
a lot of the game in the mail this
morning. Surprise I don't realise is the
first of the six men are like that not
only one staff. Public officials like
a district attorney only supposed
to do Mal you know. This is. Just
for the posted to news case and we have
to return to the center how do you like
that oh no cultures and we have to deliver
twice you're crazy. You know from folks
might think I know these
extra stamps cost only just
a few cents but yes I am finding all of
you by everybody you know if I understand
it thanks again for the letter to Kathy
Oh that's all right goodbye and thanks
again nothing can alter
hearing the welcome.
Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh you.
Know I. Know you know
how I think about it.
If.
You. Will.
Then I knew what people meant when they
said their hearts. All of us left George
and me and our marriage. In
that little pile of ashes.
I knew that from my Somehow I had to begin
to live again. But I think all I could
do was pray to Lucy. That my
my hair
.